export const allQuestions: TypeQuestions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Who founded University College London?",
    answer: "Jeremy Bentham",
    options: [
      "Charles Darwin",
      "Jeremy Bentham",
      "Isaac Newton",
      "Albert Einstein",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "In what year was UCL established?",
    answer: "1826",
    options: ["1826", "1939", "1865", "1790"],
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "What is the motto of UCL?",
    answer: "Scientia et Labore",
    options: [
      "Lux et Veritas",
      "In Hoc Signo Vinces",
      "Scientia et Labore",
      "Deo Juvante",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Which famous philosopher taught at UCL?",
    answer: "Karl Marx",
    options: [
      "Socrates",
      "Aristotle",
      "Plato",
      "Karl Marx",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Who is the current Provost of UCL?",
    answer: "David Price",
    options: [
      "Richard Horton",
      "David Price",
      "Jeremy Farrar",
      "Mark Walport",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Which UCL constituent college specializes in medical sciences?",
    answer: "UCL Faculty of Medical Sciences",
    options: [
      "UCL School of Slavonic and East European Studies",
      "UCL Institute of Education",
      "UCL Faculty of Engineering Science",
      "UCL Faculty of Medical Sciences",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "What is the name of UCL's student union?",
    answer: "UCLSU",
    options: [
      "UCL Union",
      "UCLSU",
      "UCL Student Life",
      "UCL Campus Life",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "What is the name of UCL's main library?",
    answer: "The UCL Main Library",
    options: [
      "Senate House Library",
      "British Library",
      "The Maughan Library",
      "The UCL Main Library",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Which famous writer studied at UCL?",
    answer: "Virginia Woolf",
    options: [
      "Virginia Woolf",
      "Charles Dickens",
      "William Shakespeare",
      "Oscar Wilde",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Which famous museum is located on UCL's campus?",
    answer: "The Petrie Museum of Egyptian Archaeology",
    options: [
      "British Museum",
      "Science Museum",
      "Victoria and Albert Museum",
      "The Petrie Museum of Egyptian Archaeology",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "_________ corrosion rates are found in a gas oil desulfurizers and hydrocrackers than naphtha desulfurizers and hydrocrackers by a factor of almost 2.",
    answer: "Higher",
    options: [
      "Lower",
      "Higher",
      "Sulfidization",
      "Hydrogen corrosion",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "Convert these temperatures – 156º C and 450º F",
    answer: "312º F, 232º C",
    options: [
      "304º F, 151º C",
      "284º F, 218º C",
      "312º F, 232º C",
      "296º F, 246º C",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: "300 Series SS is susceptible to LME when it comes in contact with molten ________.",
    answer: "Zinc",
    options: [
      "Cadmium",
      "Mercury",
      "Zinc",
      "Lead",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "In fired heater tubes, dissimilar weld metal cracking forms primarily on the _______ of the material.",
    answer: "Outside",
    options: [
      "Outside",
      "Inside",
      "Welds",
      "All of the above",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: "A form of mechanical fatigue in which cracks are produced as a result of dynamic loadings is _______.",
    answer: "Vibration-induced cracking",
    options: [
      "Spheroidization",
      "Vibration-induced cracking",
      "Fatigue cracking",
      "Stress cracking",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question: "The creep threshold temperature for 1 ¼, 2 ¼, 5 and 9 Cr is ________.",
    answer: "800º F",
    options: [
      "600º F",
      "700º F",
      "800º F",
      "1000º F",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question: "Thermal fatigue damage is in the form of cracking that may occur anywhere in a metallic component where relative movement is constrained, particularly under repeated __________.",
    answer: "Thermal cycling",
    options: [
      "Cyclic stresses",
      "Thermal cycling",
      "Pressure variations",
      "All of the above",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: "With sour water corrosion, at a given pressure, the HS concentration in the sour water _________ as temperatures ________.",
    answer: "Decreases, increases",
    options: [
      "Increases, increases",
      "Decreases, decreases",
      "Increases, decreases",
      "Decreases, increases",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: "Mitigation of CUI is best achieved by _________.",
    answer: "A properly applied coating system",
    options: [
      "A properly documented inspection program",
      "A properly installed insulation system",
      "A properly applied coating system",
      "A properly documented NDE program",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question: "Carburization can be confirmed by a substantial increase in hardness and a _______ in ductility.",
    answer: "Loss",
    options: [
      "Loss",
      "Gain",
      "Change",
      "None of the above",
    ],
  },
];
